T.B. Joshua Spent The Beginning
Of The New Year At The Prayer Mountain
Listen to what he has to say.
As Prophet T.B. Joshua says, see beyond your palace.
T.B. Joshua Spent The Beginning
Of The New Year At The Prayer Mountain
Viewers all over the world, Happy New Year!
I know you want to know anywhere I am, from time to time, as a man of the people.
I have been here for the past three days.
I am here because I know where I need to grow.
When we know where we need to grow, it is victory itself.
I want to pray with you.
Whatever hinders you to greatness -
it could be your weaknesses, it could be generational curses, I mean, inherited curses.
Whatever hinders you to greatness, begin to give way, in the name of Jesus!
You inherited curses, I say, give way and leave my people!
You weaknesses, bad habits in whatever way, give way, in the name of Jesus!
I remove you, in the name of Jesus!
You need a clean heart to enjoy your New Year - a right spirit within you to enjoy your New Year.
I say, whatever hinders you to greatness, give way, in the name of Jesus!
Right now, give way, in the name of Jesus!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Viewers all over the world, I like being one with nature -
where there are no disturbances, where we don't need to close our eyes to pray.
That is why I'm here; it is my habit.
That does not mean you should come to the mountain like this.
It is my habit; habit is a gift from God.
I developed this habit right from the beginning of my ministry.
When you look at my documentary, it has been like that.
When I need a quiet place, I run to the wilderness, to the mountain.
It has been my habit, right from the beginning.
It is a habit.
That does not mean you as Christians should also do the same.
You should also develop your habit; habit is a gift from God.
I am here to know the mind of God
concerning this fearful year, 2019 - very, very fearful.
I am here to know the mind of God concerning this fearful year
and also to pray for you and the world at large.
That is why I am here - heart to heart.
My viewers all over the world - heart to heart.
This is issue of heart.
Give me your heart; let us pray once again.
Whatever that does not reflect Jesus in your life, be removed, in the name of Jesus!
And begin to receive a clean heart.
Be removed, in the name of Jesus and begin to receive a right spirit within you.
Whatever that does not reflect Jesus, be removed, in the name of Jesus!
I remove them, in the name of Jesus!
Be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Christianity lies in the heart.
Whatever that does not reflect Jesus, be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Be cleansed, in the name of Jesus!
Be cleansed and receive a right spirit right now, in the name of Jesus!
Be cleansed and receive a clean heart, in the name of Jesus!
Thank You, Lord.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray. Amen.
Thank you.
I will be leaving today; I have been here for the past few days.
This is why Jesus gave me the grace to speak to you so that you would know where I am.
Thank You, Jesus.
Good Morning, viewers!
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Amen.
T.B. Joshua Spent The Beginning
Of The New Year At The Prayer Mountain
The Small Hut Prophet T.B. Joshua Stayed
During His Time At The Prayer Mountain
Viewers, this is where I managed.
The Small Hut Prophet T.B. Joshua Stayed
During His Time At The Prayer Mountain
TT: Mel Flowers 06/01/2019